newdelhiairport.in 2019-01-07

# Safety travel tips - Delhi Indternational Airport

This privacy notice applies to information we collect about you in the different sections of the website. The information we collect about you is useful to revert to you with relevant answers or to help you with a service. 

We collect the information about the following persons: : 

  * people who purchase third party services which are offered via DIAL websites, e.g. Flights and Hotels. 
  * people who subscribe or register to receive information from DIAL e.g. Airport Newsletter. 
  * people who participate in DIAL research and surveys. 
  * people who provide feedback to DIAL via our websites. 
  * job applicants . 
  * visitors to our website. 

If you are giving us your personal information in the course of purchasing, registering, or subscribing to a service or product at our website, then we will only use your information in order to provide you with that service or for closely related purposes. We use some carefully selected third parties to help us deliver these services and products to you but they are only allowed to use your personal information to deliver the service or product you have purchased, registered or subscribed to through our website. Some of our trusted third parties in supporting these services will transfer your information overseas

We will keep your personal information relating to services or products purchased in line with our retention policy which ensures that we keep your details for no longer than is necessary. Your information will be retained in a secure environment and access to it will be restricted according to the 'need to know' principle.

When you purchase certain products and services from DIAL we may send you confirmation emails; these may also include marketing which may be of interest to you. We do our best to tailor this information so that it is useful to you, but if at any time you no longer wish to receive it, you can opt out by following the instructions that we will give you with each communication. 

Complaints and Queries : 

Disclosure of personal information: In the majority of cases we will not disclose your personal information to others unless we have previously gained your consent to the same. However there will be circumstances where we may disclose your personal information without your consent e.g. where we are required by law to disclose information or where the information is required to prevent or detect a crime. In the case of all disclosures we will always ensure the disclosure is legitimate and proportionate for the purpose for which the information is sought to be disclosed. 

Visitors to our websites : 

When someone visits our websites we collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this by using cookies which record those areas of our websites that have been visited by your computer, for how long and what activity was undertaken on our website. We do this so we can understand which are the most popular parts of our websites, and also to improve your experience. We collect this information in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. 

You are not obliged to accept cookies. You have the opportunity to set your computer to either to accept all cookies, to notify you when a cookie is issued, or not to receive cookies at any time. To find out more about cookies, visit www.aboutcookies.org 

Links to other websites : 

This privacy notice does not cover the links within this site linking to other websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit.

Changes to this privacy notice : 

We keep our privacy notice under regular review and we will place any updates on this webpage. At the start of this privacy notice we will tell you when it was last updated. 1.1 These terms and conditions ("Terms") govern your viewing and use of this website (the "Website") which is owned and operated by DIAL (DIAL). For the purposes of these Terms "we", "our" and "us" refers to DIAL.
